countryroad.com.au 2019-03-18

# Privacy Policy

Country Road Clothing Pty Ltd ACN 005 419 447 is a member of the Country Road Group.

* ## Privacy commitment

Country Road Group Pty Ltd ACN 006 759 182 and its Related Bodies Corporate (as defined in the Corporations Act 2001 (Cth)) (“we”, “our” or “us”) recognise the trust you are placing in us through your dealings with us. We do everything we can to maintain that trust. Our staff are employed on the basis that they will protect information about you. Your rights to privacy are also protected by the Australian Privacy Principles in force under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). These privacy laws place strict requirements on us to treat certain information collected as confidential, to store your information securely and to allow you easy access to check and correct your information.

* ## Scope of our Privacy policy

Our Privacy Policy applies to the personal information we collect, store, maintain and use about you as our customers, visitors to our website, social media pages and other digital services (“Online Services”), or stores and members of the public. Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the brands owned by us from time to time, including, but not limited to, Country Road, Trenery, Witchery, Politix and Mimco (“Our Brands”). Personal information we collect from job applicants as part of our recruitment process is governed by our [Privacy Statement](http://www.countryroadgroup.com.au/privacy-statement).

* ## Consent

By using Our Services (as defined below), you agree to this Privacy Policy and consent to the collection and use of information by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please note that we reserve our right to amend, remove or vary this policy from time to time without notice. You should check this page regularly to take notice of any changes we may have made to this policy.

* ## When do we collect information about you?

At times, we collect personal information in the normal course of providing services for our customers.  
These services apply to our services in-store and online across Our Brands (together “Our Services”) and include:

  * Signing up to a loyalty program, membership account or newsletter subscription
  * Processing lay-by purchases
  * Accepting customer orders
  * Processing online purchases and payments
  * Registering an online account
  * Maintaining client books
  * Customer Service lines (including social media channels such as Facebook and Instagram)
  * Processing payments
  * Providing tailoring instructions
  * Ordering dry cleaning / repairs
  * Arranging product holds
  * Receiving prize application forms
  * Accepting gift voucher payments
  * Recording customer accident details
  * Processing refunds
  * Maintaining detailed information on our websites
  * Any other time where you may supply personal information to us from time to time.

We also make use of “cookies” on our websites which may collect and store personal information. A cookie is a small software message sent to your web browser by our web server. Your browser stores the message in a file and the message is then sent back to our servers each time your browser requests a page from our servers.

We use cookies to gain statistics on which areas of our sites attract traffic. We also use cookies to improve your experience of our websites. For example, cookies allow us to recognise whether or not you are returning to our websites. In addition, we make use of third parties who use cookies to serve ads based on past visits to our website. This may allow us to alert you to products or offers which we think you might be interested in viewing.

Most Internet browsers are set up to accept cookies. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you will need to adjust the settings of your browser to refuse all cookies or to notify you each time a cookie is sent to your computer. Please note that some of our Online Services will not function if your browser does not accept cookies. By using our Online Services, you consent to the use of cookies.

We use Google Analytics Advertising Features to promote our Services. Google and other third parties collect data about traffic to this site via advertising cookies and identifiers. This enables us to display ads on other sites that are relevant to you, based on your previous visits to this site. If you would like to prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, please click here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

When you click on links and banners on our sites that take you to third-party websites, you will be subject to that third-party's privacy policies. While we support the protection of privacy on the internet, we cannot be held responsible for the actions of any third-party websites.

* ## What information do we collect?

We may collect the following information from you:

  * your name and contact details, such as your physical address, email address and phone number;
  * your gender, birthdate and occupation;
  * your purchase history;
  * your company name (if applicable);
  * the name of the domain from which you access the internet;
  * the date and time you access our sites;
  * the internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our sites;
  * information about your shopping preferences/selections; and
  * any other information you may provide to us from time to time.

* ## Why do we collect this information?

We use the information to customise and provide Our Services and plan product development so that we can provide you with relevant consumer information and notify you of products and special offers that may be of interest to you across Our Brands. We also collect this information so that we may provide value-added services and marketing and remarketing across Our Brands, our Associated Entities (as defined in the Corporations Act 2001 (Cth)), including David Jones and our promotional partners through our websites, social media channels or other marketing mediums.

* ## Do we share personal information with third parties?

We may disclose information we hold to our directors, officers, employees and other Associated Entities within our corporate group for business purposes, the purpose of operating a loyalty program and marketing or remarketing purposes through our websites, social media channels or other marketing mediums.

Some of our Associated Entities with whom we share personal information may be located overseas, including in South Africa and New Zealand.

We may also disclose information to third party service providers or contractors. The countries this information may be disclosed to will vary from time to time, but may include Australia, New Zealand, South Africa, the United States of America and Japan and the European Union.

Sometimes we use third party platforms and services to process sales, store and analyse data and information, provide web support, send marketing messages, deliver products or information or to otherwise achieve the purpose for which the information was collected. These services are hosted and managed by organisations other than ourselves, and some of these services are hosted overseas. We use products and services maintained in Australia, New Zealand, USA and Japan and the European Union.

Your personal information may be stored in overseas (e.g. in data storage and cloud computing facilities operated by us (or by third parties on our behalf).We will take reasonable steps to ensure recipients of this information do not breach Australian or New Zealand Privacy laws in relation to the personal information we disclose.

Where applicable information is shared with these third parties, we will take all reasonable steps to ensure that third parties observe the confidential nature of such information and are prohibited from using any or all of this information other than for the purpose for which it was provided. We will also disclose information to a law enforcement agency if we are requested to do so by that agency in relation to suspected unlawful activity.

We will not sell or trade your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes.

* ## Promotional communications

From time to time we may use your personal information to provide you with information about our services or the services of our Associated Entities or promotional partners. We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive promotional information from us, please let us know by clicking on the “unsubscribe link”/”update your preferences” at the bottom of any of our communications, or by clicking into your account to manage the level of communication which you want to receive from us across Our Brands. Once you have told us you no longer wish to receive information about Our Services, we will no longer contact you. We will keep your basic details on our ‘do not contact’ database so that we do not contact you again.

* ## Personal information access

You may review or change personal information related to your use of Our Services. To access your information, simply sign into your account and click on your name on the top navigational menu - this will take you to "My Profile". If you would like to know what information we hold about you please contact our Privacy Manager on [privacymanager@countryroadgroup.com.au](mailto:privacymanager@countryroadgroup.com.au).

We will try to ensure that all information we collect, use or disclose about you in accordance with this Privacy Policy is accurate, complete and up-to-date. We expect that you will promptly notify us of any changes to your personal information.

If you hold multiple accounts with us through any of Our Brands’ loyalty programs, we may combine your accounts to create one profile only for each brand. Prior to doing this, we will take reasonable measures to ensure we have verified your membership details and that all the accounts belong to you.

If you discover that there is an error or information is missing, you can update your details online by signing in and visiting “My Profile” and editing the relevant details. Alternatively, if you wish to access or correct any personal information we hold about you, please contact our Privacy Manager on [privacymanager@countryroadgroup.com.au](mailto:privacymanager@countryroadgroup.com.au).

* ## Anonymity

You have the option of using a pseudonym when dealing with us so as not to identify yourself fully to us. Please bear in mind, however, that we will be unable to provide certain services to you unless you disclose your correct identity.

If you are a candidate for employment you must provide personal information which is in all respects true, accurate and up to date and is not, in any respect, misleading, deceptive or inaccurate or likely to be misleading or deceptive.

* ## Security

We understand the importance of your personal information and have appropriate procedures in place to safeguard and secure the information we collect to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information. We also take measures in respect of destroying or de-identifying personal information that is no longer needed for any lawful purpose.

We take website and credit card security extremely seriously and always endeavour to provide a secure, safe platform from which to conduct online transactions. We use the industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol, which encrypts information as it is transmitted over the internet. This encryption scrambles details such as credit card numbers, billing details and delivery addresses so that other computers are unable to decipher the information, ensuring privacy and security.

To ensure you are accessing a secure server, look for the unbroken key or closed lock symbol located either at the bottom left or top right of your browser window. If it appears, then SSL is active. You can double-check by looking at the URL. If SSL is active, then the first characters of the URL will read ‘https’ rather than just ‘http.’ It is important for you to protect against unauthorised access to your password and your computer.

Ensure you sign out when you have finished visiting our websites especially if you have accessed the websites from a shared computer.

* ## Privacy complaints

If you believe that we have breached your privacy rights in any way, or you would like to discuss any issues about our Privacy Policy please contact our Privacy Manager on 1800 801 911 or [privacymanager@countryroadgroup.com.au](mailto:privacymanager@countryroadgroup.com.au).

All such enquiries or complaints will be taken seriously and handled with impartiality and discretion.

If you wish to submit a complaint, please provide us with all relevant details such as the date and time of the incident or communication, the circumstances surrounding the event and your concerns about what was said or done. You will also receive an acknowledgment from us within 7 days confirming receipt of your complaint.

Once you have submitted your complaint we will assess it to determine whether or not you have complained about a privacy issue which is covered by the relevant privacy laws. If you have complained about something which is not appropriately dealt with under privacy law, we will write to you and explain why our Privacy Manager is unable to address your complaint.

If you have complained about something which the relevant privacy laws cover, we will thoroughly investigate all aspects of your complaint including ascertaining the relevant facts and what your expectations are for any resolution. During our investigation we may need to seek further information from you as to the nature of or factual circumstances surrounding your complaint.

We will endeavour to respond to you at all times promptly and to offer a practical solution which is consistent with our legal obligations.

If you are not satisfied with the result of your complaint to us, you can refer your complaint to the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner:  
Mail: Office of the Australian Information Commissioner GPO Box 5218, Sydney NSW 2001   
Telephone: 1300 363 992  
Email: enquiries@oaic.gov.au  
Online: <http://www.oaic.gov.au/privacy/making-a-privacy-complaint>
